<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

Your Google account may have other forms of browsing history like searches and activity from other Google services at &lt;link>myactivity.google.com&lt;/link>."</string>

For example, some websites may respond to this request by showing you ads that aren’t based on other websites you’ve visited. Many websites will still collect and use your browsing data — for example to improve security, to provide content, ads and recommendations, and to generate reporting statistics."</string>
Only someone with your passphrase can read your encrypted data. The passphrase is not sent to or stored by Google. If you forget your passphrase or want to change this setting, you’ll need to reset sync. &lt;learnmore>Learn more&lt;/learnmore>"</string>
          &lt;ul>
            &lt;li>Your browsing history
            &lt;li>Cookies and site data
            &lt;li>Information entered in forms
          &lt;/ul>"</string>
        &lt;ul>
          &lt;li>Websites you visit
          &lt;li>Your employer or school
          &lt;li>Your internet service provider
        &lt;/ul>"</string>

When you delete your browsing history — all or for a specific site — you also delete associated measurement info. See &lt;link>your browsing history&lt;/link>."</string>

When you delete your browsing history — all or for a specific site — you also delete associated measurement info. See &lt;link>your browsing history&lt;/link>."</string>

Based on your interaction with a site, like regularly signing in to an account, that site can issue a private state token to your browser. Later, if other sites you visit check for and find a valid private state token, they’re more likely to treat you like a person and not a bot.

Private state tokens improve privacy on the web and can’t be used to find out who you are."</string>

Based on your interaction with a site, like regularly signing in to an account, that site can issue a private state token to your browser. Later, if other sites you visit check for and find a valid private state token, they’re more likely to treat you like a person and not a bot.

Private state tokens improve privacy on the web and can’t be used to find out who you are."</string>
          &lt;ul>
            &lt;li>Browsing activity&lt;/li>
            &lt;li>Search history&lt;/li>
            &lt;li>Information entered in forms&lt;/li>
          &lt;/ul>"</string>
        &lt;ul>
          &lt;li>Sites and the services they use can see visits&lt;/li>
          &lt;li>Employers or schools can track browsing activity&lt;/li>
          &lt;li>Internet service providers can monitor web traffic&lt;/li>
        &lt;/ul>"</string>
To help improve the app, Chrome sends usage and crash data to Google. &lt;UMA_LINK>Manage&lt;/UMA_LINK>"</string>

If Chrome crashes, details about the crash may include some personal info

If you turn on sync, metrics may also include info about URLs you visit"</string>

To change this setting, &lt;resetlink>reset sync&lt;/resetlink>"</string>

Google gets info about the sites you set timers for and how long you visit them. This info is used to make Digital Wellbeing better."</string>
</resources>
