<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

You can always change this in Settings. Data charges may apply."</string>

Google Play will automatically collect data about how you use the app and share that data with the developer to help them improve the app."</string>

Google Play will automatically collect data about how you use the app and share that data with the developer to help them improve the app."</string>

Past edits are visible to users and the app developer unless you delete your review."</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyApxIsGO9Yw4rxdXiVm5zMpPPLJ53kz_fA</string>
    <string name="google_app_id">1:327451421140:android:9c547b5ed466b580</string>
 submitting a review!"</string>
 private feedback!"</string>

Your general area comes from your IP address, which is assigned to your device by your Internet Service Provider and is required to connect to online services. 

To let Play use your device’s location to show more relevant content and suggestions, update your settings."</string>

Your can choose if Google Play uses your approximate location in your device settings."</string>

We’re working to bring more partners to %1$s and will let you know when apps and content become available."</string>
Over"</string>
 • See your content in one place
 • Have a shortcut to what matters most

"</string>

To switch accounts and see customized content for that account, head to Play Store > Settings > Account"</string>
more"</string>
more"</string>

Google Play will automatically collect data about how you use the app and share that data with the developer to help them improve the app"</string>
    <string name="primes_marker">PrImEs</string>
    <string name="project_id">play-store-firebase</string>

&lt;a href=\"INSTALL\">Install anyway&lt;/a>"</string>

&lt;a href=\"INSTALL\">Install anyway&lt;/a>"</string>

&lt;a href=\"INSTALL\">Install anyway&lt;/a>"</string>

&lt;a href=\"INSTALL\">Install without scanning&lt;/a>"</string>

&lt;a href=\"KEEP\">Keep the app&lt;/a>"</string>

&lt;a href=\"KEEP\">Keep the app&lt;/a>"</string>

Past edits are visible to users unless you delete your review."</string>
    <string name="split_989636402">Phonesky Data Loader</string>
Google Play system update: %2$s"</string>

Latest security update from Google. Update now to keep safe and improve device stability."</string>

Your device might restart to complete the update."</string>
Try again later."</string>

"</string>
download paused"</string>

%2$s"</string>
 
Your device name is %s"</string>
The CVC is the four digits located on the front of the card, on the right side."</string>
The CVC is the last three digits of the number that appears on the back of your card in the signature bar."</string>
First turn on NFC in your settings, then tap your card to your device."</string>
</resources>
