<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="f0_deviation_entries">
        <item>Expressive</item>
        <item>Somewhat expressive</item>
        <item>Flat</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="f0_deviation_values">
        <item>1.0</item>
        <item>0.5</item>
        <item>0.0</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="language_detection_entries">
        <item>Off</item>
        <item>Conservative</item>
        <item>Aggressive</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="language_detection_values">
        <item>off</item>
        <item>script</item>
        <item>always</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tts_example_strings">
        <item>ar:هذا مِثالٌ لتوليد الكلام في اللغة العَرَبيِّة</item>
        <item>bn:বাংলায় কথা বলার জন্য এটি একটি উদাহরণ</item>
        <item>da:Dette er et eksempel på talesyntese på dansk.</item>
        <item>de:Dies ist ein Beispiel für Sprachsynthese in Deutsch.</item>
        <item>cs:Toto je příklad hlasové syntézy v češtině.</item>
        <item>el:Παράδειγμα σύνθεσης φωνής στα Ελληνικά.</item>
        <item>en:This is an example of speech synthesis in English.</item>
        <item>es:Este es un ejemplo de síntesis de voz en español.</item>
        <item>et:See on eesti keele kõnesünteesi näidis.</item>
        <item>fi:Tässä on esimerkki suomenkielisestä puhesynteesistä.</item>
        <item>fil:Isa itong halimbawa ng pangungusap sa wikang Filipino.</item>
        <item>fr:Voici un échantillon de synthèse vocale en français.</item>
        <item>hi:यह हिन्दी में भाषण संश्लेषण का एक उदाहरण है</item>
        <item>hu:Ez egy szintetizált mondat magyar nyelven.</item>
        <item>in:ini adalah contoh sintesis suara dalam bahasa Indonesia</item>
        <item>it:Questo è un esempio di sintesi vocale in italiano.</item>
        <item>ja:こちらが日本語音声合成のサンプルです。</item>
        <item>jv:Iki conto sintesis swara ing Basa Jawa</item>
        <item>ko:이것은 한국어 음성 합성의 예입니다.</item>
        <item>km:នេះគឺជាឧទាហរណ៍មួយនៃការសំយោគសម្លេងជាភាសាខ្មែរ</item>
        <item>nb:Dette er et eksempel på talesyntese på norsk.</item>
        <item>ne:यो नेपाली बोलीको एक उदाहरण हो।</item>
        <item>nl:Dit is een voorbeeld van spraaksynthese in het Nederlands.</item>
        <item>pl:To jest przykład syntezy mowy w języku polskim.</item>
        <item>pt:Isto é um exemplo de síntese de voz em Português.</item>
        <item>ro:Acesta este un exemplu de voce sintetizată în limba română.</item>
        <item>ru:Вы слушаете синтез речи на русском языке.</item>
        <item>si:මේ කථන සංකලනයට උදාහරණයකි සිංහල</item>
        <item>sk:Toto je ukážka hlasovej syntézy v slovenčine.</item>
        <item>su:Ieu conto sintesis sora dina Basa Sunda</item>
        <item>sv:Detta är ett exempel på talsyntes på svenska.</item>
        <item>th:นี่คือตัวอย่างการสังเคราะห์เสียงในภาษาไทย.</item>
        <item>tr:Bu bir Türkçe konuşma sentezi örneğidir</item>
        <item>uk:Це приклад синтезу української мови</item>
        <item>vi:Đây là một ví dụ của việc tổng hợp lời nói tiếng Việt.</item>
        <item>zh:這是一個中文語音合成的範例</item>
        <item>yue:這是一個廣東話語音合成的範例</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
